https://www.gurnick.edu/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentPrograms and CoursesCertificate ProgramsDental Assistant ProgramMedical Assistant ProgramMedical Assistant With Phlebotomy ProgramDiploma ProgramsLimited X-Ray Technician with MA Skills ProgramPsychiatric Technician ProgramVocational Nurse ProgramAssociate Degree ProgramsA.S. in Magnetic Resonance Imaging ProgramA.S. in Nursing ProgramA.S. in Physical Therapist Assistant ProgramA.O.S. in Radiologic Technology ProgramA.S. in Radiologic Technology ProgramA.O.S. in Ultrasound Technology ProgramA.S. in Vocational Nursing ProgramBachelor's Degree ProgramsB.S. in Diagnostic Medical Imaging ProgramB.S. in Nursing (BSN) ProgramRN to BSN ProgramContinuing Education CoursesCPR for Basic Life Support CourseIV Therapy and Blood Withdrawal CourseInternational CoursesInternational Nurse Graduate CoursesCampus LocationsOnline LearningConcord CampusFresno CampusModesto CampusSacramento CampusSan Mateo CampusVan Nuys CampusCorporate OfficeStudentsCatalog and AddendumCareer Services DepartmentForeign Transcript EvaluationsGeneral Admission RequirementsHoliday ScheduleReplacement Diploma RequestStudent FormsStudent Services DepartmentTranscript RequestVeterans BenefitsFinancialCost of AttendanceFinancial AidMake an Online PaymentNet Price CalculatorResourcesBrochuresCareer Training VideosCOVID-19 Resources and FAQsDistance Education RequirementsEvent VideosHealthcare Career BlogNewsPoliciesRequired DisclosuresStudent TestimonialsAbout UsAccreditation and ApprovalClinical RotationsFaculty and StaffFrom the Desk of the CEOHire a Gurnick GraduateMission StatementWhy Students Choose GurnickWork at GurnickStudent LoginGurnick EdgeGurnick Online (Moodle)Student PortalADB/Complio Immunization Tracking Read the Latest COVID-19 UpdatesEnroll Now & Take Classes From Home Apply Now Take a Virtual TourPrivacy PolicyStart your new
career right here.Your Name*
First Name
Last Name Email* Phone*Campus of Interest*Select a CampusOnlineSan Mateo CampusConcord CampusModesto CampusFresno CampusSacramento CampusVan Nuys CampusProgram of Interest*Program of InterestSelect Campus FirstOn-Ground Clinical Site*On-Ground Clinical SiteLos Angeles, CAFresno, CAPhoenix, AZ* I agree to be contacted by a Gurnick Academy representative. Message and data rates apply.CommentsThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Website AccessThis Terms of Service Agreement (from now on “Agreement”) sets forth the terms and conditions by which we, Gurnick Academy, provide the www.gurnick.edu Informational Services to site visitors, users, registered and prospective students, and account holders. By visiting our site, using any of the tools and services provided via our website, or registering an account, you, as a result of this Agreement, be bound by each of the terms and conditions of this Agreement.We may automatically amend this Agreement at any time by informing you of the amended terms via email to an email address you provide to us if you are a registered account holder. Such amendments will be effective when sent to your last known email address. You must keep your email address up to date, maintain a valid email address, and ensure that the emails we send you are not filtered or stopped by spam filters or other types of email blocking functionalities. Alternatively, we may merely post the amended terms and make them available to be read by current account holders. In such cases, the modified terms and conditions are effective and in force when posted by us.For those visitors who have not registered as users, it is their responsibility to read these Terms of Service each time they access any portion of our site. Any usage of this site by you, including merely viewing our home page or any page published on our site, as an unregistered user, means that you agree to be bound by every one of the terms and conditions of this Terms of Service Agreement.CopyrightThe information on this Web site is protected by copyright: Copyright 2004 — 2020 Gurnick Academy. All Rights Reserved.Except as expressly permitted herein, no portion of the information on this Web site may be reproduced in any form or by any means without prior written permission from Gurnick Academy.Privacy StatementGurnick Academy will never knowingly divulge personal information acquired through our website to any third party other than selected affiliated facilities, law enforcement agencies, and other parties if required by law.We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities.Employees and Agents of Gurnick Academy who have access to personally identifiable information must protect this information consistent with this Privacy Notice. Employees protect PII by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing at Gurnick Academy.Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information we collect will never be disclosed inconsistently with this Privacy Notice.To enhance your experience with our site, some of our web pages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. By themselves, Cookies do not tell us your email address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, filling out our online request. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g., automatically fill out the request form for you, etc.).Our website uses the Google and Facebook remarking service to advertise on third party websites across the Internet (including Google and Facebook) to previous visitors to our website. It could mean that we advertise to previous site visitors, for example, haven’t filled out a request info form. Third-party vendors use cookies to serve ads based on user’s past visits. These vendors don’t have access to any personal information. Any personal data collected through our request form or by phone will be used per our privacy policy. If you want to opt-out of Google’s use of cookies, please visit Google’s Ads Settings. If you wish to opt-out of Facebook ads, please visit this page. Alternatively, you can opt-out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.Third-Party LinksLinks to third-party websites on this website are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave the Gurnick Academy website. We do not review all third-party sites. Thus we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any website which we do not directly control.Limited WarrantyGurnick Academy makes no representations about the suitability of the information contained in www.gurnick.edu.Products are provided “as is” without representations or warranties of any kind, either express or implied, including, but not limited to implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, and non-infringement. In no event will Gurnick Academy be liable to you for any incidental, indirect, special, or consequential damages (even if Gurnick Academy has been advised of the possibility of such damages) arising out of the use or inability to use the www.gurnick.edu site.While our staff strives to provide accurate information to our site users, we make no guarantees regarding this content’s accuracy or reliability.Gurnick Academy reserves the right to change regulations, policies, fees, calendars, and revise curricula deemed necessary and desirable. Since the information contained herein is subject to change, this website should not be considered a contract between Gurnick Academy and the student. © Copyright 2020 Gurnick Academy Disclosures Privacy Policy Sitemap CCPA CARES Act Reports Is Healthcare Career Training Right for You? Take the Free Quiz!
